Virgil Hoyt McClintock papers, Inclusive: 1911-1952, undated, Bulk: 1945-1951, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Reference Materials, 1911-1951, undated; 2
  - Published Materials: "Outline of Procedure for Trial of Certain War Criminals", undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Published Materials: A Pocket Guide to France, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Published Materials: "United States v. Friedrich Becker et al: Review and Recommendations", undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Legal Memoranda, 1942-1953, undated; 3
  General condition: Poor.
  This series contains various materials relating to V.H. McClintock’s legal work in Germany.
  - "Mr. McClintock Personal" (1 of 3), 1946-1947, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Mr. McClintock Personal" (2 of 3), 1946-1947, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "Mr. McClintock Personal" (3 of 3), 1946-1947, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "International Military Tribunal Document Book": Case Against the SS (1 of 7), circa 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "International Military Tribunal Document Book": Case Against the SS (2 of 7), circa 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - International Military Tribunal Document Book: Case Against the SS (3 of 7), circa 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - International Military Tribunal Document Book: Case Against the SS (4 of 7), circa 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - International Military Tribunal Document Book: Case Against the SS (5 of 7), circa 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - International Military Tribunal Document Book: Case Against the SS (6 of 7), circa 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - International Military Tribunal Document Book: Case Against the SS (7 of 7), circa 1942-1946 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda (1 of 5), circa 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda (2 of 5), circa 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda (3 of 5), circa 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda (4 of 5), circa 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda (5 of 5), circa 1946-1953 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper: The Stars and Stripes, 1951 February 1-2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Personal, 1947-1950, undated; 4
  This series contains correspondence, financial documents, photographs, and other material related to V.H. McClintock’s personal life during his years in Germany.
  - Correspondence, 1936-1950 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Financial Documents, 1948-1950, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Literary Productions, 1947-1948, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Notepads, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Metal Keys, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - General, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Scrapbooks, 1945-1947; 5
  General condition: Good.
  This series contains two scrapbooks documenting, in photographs, the Dachau Trials of 1945-1947.
  - War Crimes Trials Scrapbook #1: Dachau Concentration Camp: Page 1-4, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - War Crimes Trials Scrapbook #1: Malmedy Case: Page 5-8, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - War Crimes Trials Scrapbook #1: Mauthausen Concentration Camp: Page 9-11, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - War Crimes Trials Scrapbook #1: Flossenburg Concentration Camp: Page 12-15, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - War Crimes Trials Scrapbook #1: Buchenwald near Weimar Concentration Camp: Page 16-22, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - War Crimes Scrapbook #2: Page 1-7, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - War Crimes Scrapbook #2: Page 8-15, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Books, 1933-1943, undated; 6
  This series contains books related to V.H. McClintock’s legal work in Germany, as well as propaganda books printed during the rise of the NAZI party.
  - Log Book, 1950 January 23 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - McClintock Review Docket, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Ich Kämpfe, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Adolf Hitler: Bilder Aus Dem Leben Des Führers, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Deutschland Erwacht: Werden, Kampf und Sieg Der NSDAP, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 2)